neoncams.com 2011-05-14

# Privacy Policy - NeonCams

## Welcome **Guest** to NeonCams!

**NeonCams** is the home of the hot sexy live amateur webcam models online. Join now to access the live webcam sex shows and enjoy the unique visual and sexual experience. Click here to find out why you should join **NeonCams**.

## **NeonCams Privacy Policy**

[NeonCams](http://www.neoncams.com/ "NeonCams") is committed to maintaining a privacy policy that benefits each individual customer's preferences.

**NOTE: Our privacy policy is null and void in cases of fraud!**

This policy explains the privacy practices for [NeonCams](http://www.neoncams.com/ "NeonCams") (hereinafter referred to as "NeonCams", "site", "our", "we", or "us"). In order to provide interactive computer billing and fraud services, NeonCams collects and uses certain information about you. This policy explains what we collect, what we use and how you can interact with NeonCams in order to ensure the accuracy of the data we collect and use.

  1. **Information Collection:** Visitors can access our Web site home page and browse our Web site without disclosing any personal data. However, in order to provide you with a particular product or service online, NeonCams may request that you voluntarily supply NeonCams with primary personal data (such as name and email address) and identifiers (such as web site password). NeonCams gives you the option of using a secure transmission method of sending such information.  
NeonCams receives and stores your IP Address, and NeonCams also employs its software in order to ascertain your physical location before making a purchase. However, we do not collect information from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. You are required to provide NeonCams with accurate and up-to-date information, and failure to provide NeonCams with such information could result in voiding your Agreement with NeonCams.
  2. **Information Use:** NeonCams is the sole owner of the information collected on its sites. NeonCams will not sell, share, or rent this information to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed it this policy. NeonCams shall release data when required by law, to enforce its Agreement or the contract rights of its clients. NeonCams shares the following data from you: your e-mail address, your username and password and your agreement to be bound by NeonCams terms and conditions. NeonCams uses the data it collects for the technical administration of the Web site, research and development, and fraud deterrence.
  3. **Information sharing:** We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to governmental institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.
  4. **Email correspondence:** NeonCams may request a confirmation when you receive and open and e-mail communication delivered by NeonCams. We archive and identify the origination IP address of all email sent into our network.
  5. **Third party information:** Occasionally, NeonCams receives information from third parties to compare it to information that you had provided to NeonCams for fraud prevention purposes.
  6. **Cookies:** A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor. NeonCams employs "cookie" technology. We use Cookie to store personal data, to authenticate you as a Site user, for security purposes, and to track our affiliate click-throughs and sign-up rate.
  7. **Children:** NeonCams does not request, or knowingly collect, personal data from anyone under the **age of 18**. Furthermore, NeonCams does not knowingly give children the ability to post messages or otherwise distribute information about themselves on our web site.
  8. **Security:** We take every precaution to protect our visitors' information. We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction, or accidental loss. NeonCams utilizes Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software when receiving and transmitting electronic payments. NeonCams encrypts the information that you provided.   
In addition, NeonCams does everything to protect your information off-linee. All employees and data processors who have access to, and are associated with, the processing of personal data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. NeonCams employs a username and password scheme in order to limit and achieve access to our computer network by our employees and third parties.

If you have an inquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact us at the address below:

CCCV Ltd.(UK Limited) 1st Floor, Granby Centre Eversley Street, Liverpool L8 2TU, United Kingdom. help [ @ ] cccvltd.com
